(Sheldon:)You're only saying that
because you haven't been there.
(Sheldon:)I am now a hexagon
in two-dimensional space...
(Sheldon:)...and can only perceive the edges
of other objects.
(Raj:)Oy.
(Sheldon:)Is that you, Raj?
I don't recognize your edge.
(Raj:)Sheldon, I'm begging you.
(Raj:)I want to go to this mixer,
and I don't want to go alone.
(Sheldon:)Well, you're in luck.
There's a mixer here in Flatland.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look.
(Sheldon:)There's a sexually attractive
line segment.
(Sheldon:)-Chat her up.
-What?
(Sheldon:)Tell her you're a circle.
Flatland gals are all hot for circles.
(Leonard:)I hope you're hungry.
We're going to a terrific restaurant.
(Bernadette:)Oh, yeah, I'm starved.
When you spend all day in a bio lab...
(Bernadette:)...watching flesh-eating bacteria
skeletonize rodents...
(Bernadette:)...it really works up an appetite.
(Bernadette:)Flesh-eating bacteria
and yet I still wanna kiss this woman.